FASAN OLUWABUKOLA AJIKE

Lagos, Nigeria. oluwabukola.fasan@gmail.com 08080110323, 07065103467

Career Objective

I am a passionate front-end developer willing to contribute to the efficiency of the team via commitment, hard work, attention to detail, and superior organisational abilities. I have expertise in web development and UI/UX design as well as a thorough grasp of computers and technology connected to computing, driven to grow professionally and achieve success in the tech industry.

Skills

- HTML
- Figma and Corel Draw.
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Typescript
- React
- Next

Education

B.SC Computer Science (Second Class Upper Division)

Federal University Oye- Ekiti, Ekiti state. 2015-2019

Other Certifications

Software Development (Front-end Development)

Stutern, Lagos State. 2022-2023

Certificate of Completion (Product Design)

Zuri Inc., Lagos State. 2022

Certificate in Introduction to UI/UX

Geneza School of design, Lagos State. 2022

Experience

☐ Front-End Developer Intern Sabi Programmers, Akure, Ondo State, Nigeria

July 2023- November 2023

- Developed and maintained user-interface using HTML, CSS, Javascript and React.
- Created UI components with resuable codes for a better user experience
- Building the client's side of the web application
- Built a portfolio app and a quiz application.

☐ UI/UX Designer

Onract Limited, Manchester, England, United Kingdom (Remote).

December 2022- December 2023

- Gather and evaluate user requirements in collaboration with product managers and engineers
- Develop UI mockups and prototypes that clearly illustrate how sites function and look like
- Adhere to style standards on fonts, colours and images
- Develop UI mockups and prototypes that clearly illustrate how sites function and would look like

☐ Product Designer (Intern) Zuri Inc-Ingressive for Good, Africa.

March 2022- June 2022

- Designed a Mobile Management system for task management
- Conducted User Research on Logistics Industry
- Team collaboration on the designing authentication codes Library

Leadership Experience

2019-2020 Vice President, Nigeria Association of Computer Science Students (FUOYE chapter).

2018-2019 Assistant Librarian, Nigeria Association of Computer Science Students

(FUOYE chapter).